ece.org 2019-01-18

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how we use and protect any information you provide when using the Website.

**Additionally, when applicable, ECE will process personal data in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).**

**We are committed to protecting your privacy.**

Any identifying information you provide while using the Website will be used only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**What information we collect**

This applies to all information collected or submitted on the ECE® website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information that may be collected at these pages are: name, mailing address, email address, phone number, credit/debit Card information, gender, educational history, company name.

**Credit Cards**  
We do not record or store credit card numbers, physically or electronically. Credit card numbers used to make payments to us via our website or over the telephone are submitted directly to, and processed exclusively by, an independent, secure payment gateway called Authorize.Net.

**Chat Communications**  
A customer may communicate with our Customer Service Representatives via LiveChat. Communications made via LiveChat may be recorded for quality control and customer service purposes but will not be shared with outside parties.

**What we do with the information we gather**

We use this information to understand your needs and provide better services, as well as for the following reasons: internal record keeping; improving our products and services; and periodically sending promotional emails about products and services, special offers, or other information related to international education. We may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.

We will not sell, release, distribute, or lease your personal information to other parties unless we have your permission or are required to do so by law. We may use your personal information to send you information about products, services, or events related to international education, or for market research purposes.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

If you have an account with us, you can log into your account to change information.  Or, you can click on "Send Us Your Question" below.

**Security  **

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of information, we have implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file that may be placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can analyze web traffic and allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by identifying and remembering information about your preferences.

We use cookies on this Website to save individual user preferences and not for any other purpose. Overall, cookies help us to improve the Website. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, aside from the data you share with us.

**Links to other sites**

Our Website may contain links to other sites of interest. If you use these links to leave our Website, please note that we have no control over these outside sites and that this Privacy Policy is not applicable to them. Therefore, we are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites. You should exercise caution and review the privacy statements of the sites in question.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify or supplement the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Changes to our Privacy Policy will be posted in this section of our Website and can be reviewed at any time.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 414-289-3400 or click on "Send Us Your Question" below.
